<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cirta</string>
    <string name="Home_titel">Constantine – The City of Hanging Bridges</string>
    <string name="cirta_description">
        It is the third-largest city in Algeria and the capital of the country’s eastern region.
        Known as the City of Hanging Bridges due to its unique geographical landscape, it is built on a solid limestone rock, giving it a distinctive appearance and earning it the title "The City of Ancient Rock."\n\n
        With a history spanning over 2,300 years, it was originally known as Cirta and served as the capital of the Kingdom of Numidia before falling under Roman rule.\n
        It received its current name in 313 AD in honor of Emperor Constantine the Great.\n
        Throughout the centuries, it remained an important cultural and historical center, preserving its rich heritage to this day.
    </string>
    <string name="Hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="Restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="Tourist">Tourist Attractions</string>
    <string name="Transportation">Transportation</string>
    <string name="about">About the app</string>
    <string name="students">Students</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="historical_landmarks">Historical Landmarks</string>
    <string name="natural_sites">Natural Sites</string>
    <string name="bridges">Bridges</string>
    <string name="cultural_religious_sites">Cultural &amp; Religious Sites</string>

    <!-- Bridge Names -->
    <string name="sidi_mcid">Sidi M’Cid Bridge</string>
    <string name="sidi_rached">Sidi Rached Bridge</string>
    <string name="el_kantara">El-Kantara Bridge</string>
    <string name="pont_des_chutes">Falls Bridge</string>
    <string name="bab_el_kantra">Bab El Kantra Bridge</string>

    <!-- Bridge Descriptions in English -->
    <string name="sidi_mcid_desc">The highest bridge in Constantine, standing 175 meters above the Rhumel Gorge. Built in 1912, it was once the highest suspension bridge in the world.</string>
    <string name="sidi_rached_desc">A stunning stone-arch bridge built in 1912, featuring 27 arches and standing 105 meters high. It was once the largest stone bridge in the world.</string>
    <string name="el_kantara_desc">One of Constantine’s oldest bridges, dating back to the Roman era. It has been rebuilt multiple times, serving as a historic passageway into the city.</string>
    <string name="pont_des_chutes_desc">Named after the waterfalls it crosses, this 1925 bridge allows vehicles and pedestrians to admire the natural beauty of Constantine.</string>
    <string name="bab_el_kantra_desc">Originally built by the Ottomans in 1792 and rebuilt in 1863, this bridge serves as an important gateway to the old city.</string>

    <!-- Bridge Locations in English -->
    <string name="sidi_mcid_location">Located in the Sidi M’Cid district, Constantine Municipality. It connects the city center to the heights of Sidi M’Cid, near the University Hospital of Constantine.</string>
    <string name="sidi_rached_location">Located in the downtown area of Constantine, it connects the city center to the Plateau of Mansourah, near the Constantine train station.</string>
    <string name="el_kantara_location">Located in the Bab El Kantara district, Constantine Municipality. It connects the lower part of the city with the old medina, near Emir Abdelkader Mosque.</string>
    <string name="pont_des_chutes_location">Located near the Boumerzoug district, Constantine Municipality. It spans over the waterfalls of the Rhumel River, offering a scenic view of the valley.</string>
    <string name="bab_el_kantra_location">Located in the Bab El Kantara district, Constantine Municipality. It serves as the historical entrance to the city, near the ancient Ottoman fortress.</string>

    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="location_btn">See in Map</string>
</resources>
